PRINCE JOSE

DIPLOMA IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING WITH 3 YRS OF EXPERIENCE

Contact no: +91-8089400992 E-mail: jose.prince19@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Diploma holder in Mechanical Engineer with 3 yrs of experience is seeking for permanent job, to be an employee where I can contribute my skills and experience to the further development of the organization and achieve growth in my professional career.

EXPERIENCE

Sona Comstar (Chennai, TN, IN)

Still Working from Aug 2021

- Team leader
- Manage team
- Organize team
- Working on Electronic Vehicle section(Hub Wheel)
- Ensure Team Safety
- Ensure quality and production output at the same time
- Report quality issues.

AVG Group of Company (Adoor, Kerala, IN)

Nov 2019 to Jan 2021 (1YR 2M)

- Service Advisor...
- Greet customers and offer excellent customer service from intake to release of their vehicles.
- Determine and diagnose car issues based on customer description and vehicle condition.
- Handle and resolve customer complaints regarding services.
- Maintain customer records and enter data into computer databases.

Rane TRW Power Steering System PVT LTD (Chennai, TN, IN)

Sep 2018 to Sep 2019 (1YR)

- Neem trainee
- Check child parts quality.

- Inspect the child parts and separate ok parts.
- Ok parts move to assembly section.
- Should inspect each part 100%

Mar Ivanious PVT ITI (Seethathodu, Kerala, IN)

Feb 2018 to Aug 2018 (6 M)

- Trade theory Instructor.
- Subjects: Automobile Engineering, Electronics

Kerala State Road transport Co-operation (K.S.R.T.C) (Ranni, Kerala, IN)

Feb 2017 to Feb 2018 (1YR)

- Apprentice trainee
- Daily Checkup of scheduled vehicles.
- Maintains work based on scheduled and based on driver's daily report.
- Support Senior Mechanics.

QUALIFICATION

DIPLOMA IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING (2016)

Udaya Institute of Technology (Ammandivilai, Nagercoil, TN, IN) Anna University

Project (Automatic Hand Brake System)
 Sometimes we ignore to put vehicle hand brake while the vehicle stops, this system automatically put's hand break while the ignition key turns off.

HSE (PLUS TWO) (2014)

Gov. HSS (Kadumeenchira, Pathanamthitta, Kerala, IN) Kerala State Educational Board

SSLC (10th) (2012)

T.T.T.M.V.H.S.S (Vadasserikkara, Pathanamthitta, Kerala, IN) Kerala State Educational Board

SKILL'S / HOBBIES

- Quick leaner
- Ability to deal with people diplomatically
- Good communication skill

- Computer
- Team Management
- Trainer
- Team organization
- Computer
- Electronics
- Singing

LANGUAGE KNOWN

English (Read, Write, Speak)Malayalam (Read, Write, Speak)

Tamil (Speak)

Hindi (Read, Write)

PERSONAL DETAILS

➤ Father's Name - Jose Issac

Mother's Name - Chinnamma Jose
 Date of Birth - 19/AUG/1996

Gender - Male
 Father's occupation - Driver
 Mother's Occupation - House wife
 Nationality - Indian
 Marital Status - Single
 Religion - Christian

➤ Driving license no. - 62/3362/2016 (M/C with gr, 3whlr, LMV)

➤ Passport no. - N9534807

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that above mentioned information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

PLACE Yours's truly,

DATE PRINCE JOSE